Contact

peffinger11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/portiaeffinger-msn-aprn-fnp-c-90487891 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service

Compliance

Pediatrics

Certifications

Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP)

Portia Effinger MSN, APRN FNP-C

Nurse Practitioner

Greater Atlanta Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the health care industry and community at large. Skilled in Microsoft Word, various EMR platforms, Acute Care, Primarycare management, leadership, and peer Mentorship. Strong healthcare service professional with a Master of Science - MS focused in Family Practice Nurse/Nursing from Kennesaw State University.

Experience

Wingard Urgent Care & Wellness Nurse Practitioner October 2019 - Present (10 months)

Atlanta Metropolitan Area

Provide patient centered care in structured clinical setting to all age groups. Care ranges from primary care services to urgent care matters.

The Recharge Project, Inc Founder February 2020 - Present (6 months)

Atlanta Metropolitan Area

Leader of a Nonprofit organization that aims to assist metro Atlanta's youth with the emotional struggles of grief after experiencing the loss of a parent or primary caregiver. Organizing monthly meet ups that promote healthy coping mechanisms, relationship building, mentorship and youth empowerment.

Children's Healthcare of Atlanta

RN

July 2013 - May 2020 (6 years 11 months)

Work with a structured healthcare team to aid in the recovery process of critically ill pediatric patients in an acute care setting.

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions

RN

December 2017 - October 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Greater Atlanta Area

Assist with filling staffing needs within various metropolitan area hospitals on a Per diem basis.

Aureus Medical Group Travel RN August 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 1 month) United States

Assist/fill-in at understaffed medical facilities.

Grady Health System
Staff nurse
March 2012 - July 2013 (1 year 5 months)

Plan, implement, and carry out health care objectives specific to patient diagnosis, to assist in recover and stabilization.

Education

Kennesaw State University

Master of Science - MS, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2017 - 2018)

Grambling State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007 - 2011)

McEachern High School High School Diploma · (2003 - 2007)